James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 1: Political Activity, 1957 – 1985
  - Series 4 U.S. House of Representatives, 1982 – 1985
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Editorials—“Armageddon II”, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Editorials—“Heroic Materialism,”, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Editorials—“Who is Buddy McCay and what is he doing in Congress?”, No Date (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Editorials—“Deregulation and Sauk Centres,”, No Date (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Expenses, December 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Farm bill, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—98th Congress—Legislative Profile (pp. 1-103), January 3, 1983-November 9, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—98th Congress—Legislative Profile (pp. 104-200), January 3, 1983-November 9, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—98th Congress—Legislative Profile (pp. 201-282), January 3, 1983-November 9, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Letters from Washington, December 20, 1982-December 20, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Letters from Washington, January 24, 1984-October 4, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Member’s individual voting record—98th Congress, 1st session, No Date (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Member’s individual voting record—98th Congress, 2nd session, No Date (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Memorandum, December 22, 1983-June 18, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Miscellaneous quotes, No Date (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—National House Democratic Caucus, January 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—National Republican Congressional Committee, No Date (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Newsletter, March 1983-December 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Paper written by Michael McNulty, Ireland, No Date (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Presidents task force on International Private Enterprise, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Roll call subject guide—98th Congress, 1st session (pp. 1-70), No Date (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Roll call subject guide—98th Congress, 2nd session (pp. 71-128), No Date (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Roll call subject guide—98th Congress, 2nd session, No Date (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Voting Record, No Date (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Voting Record—98th Congress, 1st session, No Date (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - U.S. House of Representatives—Water Resource Development, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Quarterly, Weekly Report, vol. 41, no. 1, The House Class of 1982, January 8, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - U.S. House of Representatives – House Rules and Manual (Inscribed), No Date (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - U.S. House of Representatives - House Resolutions 1652-2109, 98th Congress, 1st Session, February 24, 1983-March 15, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives - House Resolutions 2118-4566, 98th Congress, 1st Session, March 16, 1983-November 18, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - U.S. House of Representatives – Directory of New Democratic Members, 98th Congress, No Date (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - U.S. House of Representatives – Hearings regarding U.S. assistance to foreign copper producers, May 20, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - U.S. House of Representatives – Whip Issue Summary, 98th Congress, September 26, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - U.S. House of Representatives – “An Act to authorize an ongoing program of water resources research, January 23, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Subgroup 2: Volunteer Activity, 1958-1983
  "Volunteer Activity," consists of material covering his volunteer activities from 1958-1983. Series One consists of his involvement with the 4-H Club. This series includes correspondence and reports. Series Two contains material regarding McNulty’s involvement with the Arizona Board of Regents (1980-1983). This series contains correspondence, budget requests, reports, intercollegiate athletics, minutes, and search committee for selecting a new president. Series Three consists of materials relating to the Arizona State Bar Association (1958-1979). This series contains mostly correspondence and minutes. Series Four is the Arizona State Board of Education (1965-1977). This series contains mostly correspondence and minutes. Series Five includes material documenting McNulty’s involvement with the Catholic Church. Series Six contains material relating to his involvement with the Cochise County Hospital Association and the Copper Queen Hospital Association. Series Seven contains material relating to McNulty’s involvement with the Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona (1976-1978). Series Eight contains records documenting McNulty's involvement with the Arizona State Hospital (1958-1965). This series contains correspondence as well as meeting minutes as well as reports. Because of the sensitive nature of the material, these items have been sealed until 2028. Series Nine consists of records created during his involvement with the League of Arizona Cities and Towns (1958-1960). Series Ten consists of records created during his involvement with the University of Arizona College of Law (1967-1979). Series Eleven contains miscellaneous organizations that McNulty was involved with between the1950’s-1970’s.
  - Series 1: 4-H Club, 1966 – 1977
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Arizona Youth Foundation Board of Trustees Budgets, 1974 – 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Arizona Youth Foundation Board of Trustees Officers, 1976 – 1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Arizona Youth Foundation Minutes, 1975 – 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Arizona Youth Foundation Reports: “The Arizona 4-H Program,” “Trends In The Arizona 4-H Program: 1960-1974.” Analysis of 4-H Needs in the 1970s,”, No Date (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Articles of Incorporation, No Date (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Award, No Date (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Baseball, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, July 1966-December 1966 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, January 1967-October 1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, January 1968-October 1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, December 1974 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, January 1975-March 1975 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, April 1975-August 1975 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, September 1975-December 1975 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, January 1976-June 1976 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, July 1976-December 1976 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, January 1977-September 1977 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, October 1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, November 1977 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, December 1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Correspondence, February 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—County By-Laws, 1972, 1974, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Fundraising Pamphlets and Brochures, No Date (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Operations Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Pamphlet, No Date (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “4-H in Century III,”, No Date (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “Annual 4-H Yearbook,”, 1974–1975, 1975–1976, 1976–1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “Cochise County Agriculture,”, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “Freedom To Be: Arizona’s Investment In Tomorrow.”, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “Handbook For Local Leaders,”, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H Club—Publications: “Is Youth in Social Turmoil,”, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Pamphlet—Freedom, No Date (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Publications—National 4-H Council Program and Services, No Date (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Publications—“Tax Exempt Status,”, No Date (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Activity—4-H-Club—Stationary, No Date (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Series 2: Arizona Board of Regents, 1980-1983
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Accreditation Of College Of Mines Academic Curricula, November 1980 - September 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Accreditation Of College Of Mines Academic Curricula, Mining Industry, May 1981 - July 1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Accreditation Of College Of Mines Academic Curricula, Publications, 1978 - 1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Agenda, October 1982 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Agreement with Arizona Wranglers franchise, September 29, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Agriculture Subcommittee, 1979 - 1981 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget requests, No Date (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget requests, notes, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget requests, summary, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget reports--University of Arizona, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget Reports--Northern Arizona University, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Budget Reports, Arizona State University, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Bylaws Recodification, No Date (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Committee On Engineering At Arizona State University, June 1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Committee On University Competition With Private Enterprise, 1978 - 1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Committee On University Competition With Private Enterprise, February 1981 - September 1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Committee On University Competition With Private Enterprise - Solar Energy, February 1981 - March 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Committee On University Competition With Private Enterprise - Solar Energy, April 1981 - May 1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, September 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, October 1-9, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, October 10-31, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, November 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, December 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, January 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, February 1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, March 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, April 1981 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, May 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, June 1981 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, July 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, August 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, September 1-9, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, September 11-29, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, October 1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, November 1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, December 1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, January 1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, February 1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, March 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, April 1982 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, May 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, June 1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, July 1982 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, September 1982 - October 1982 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, November 1982 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, December 1982 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Correspondence, January 1983 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Expenses, October 14, 1980-June 3, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Expenses, June 5, 1981-October 14, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Expenses, October 16, 1981-April 12, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Expenses, April 19, 1982-January 13, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Finance subcommittee—Correspondence, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Finance subcommittee—Legislative budget requests, September 29, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Finance subcommittee—minutes, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Inauguration of J. Russell Nelson, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, November 1978, November 1979, January 1981 - March 1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, April 1981 - May 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, June 1981 - July 1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, August 1981 - September 1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, October 1981 - December 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Intercollegiate Athletics, January 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Intercollegiate Athletics, Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents--Intercollegiate Athletics, Publications, 1979 - 1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Local fund budgets—University of Arizona, May 22, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Local fund budgets—Arizona State University, May 21, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Local fund budgets—Northern Arizona University, May 21, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, September 1979 - November 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, January 1980 - September 1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, October 1980 - December 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, January 1981 - May 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, July 1981 - December 1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, January 1982 - June 1982 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Meeting Minutes, July 1982 - October 1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—“Program for Academic Excellence,”, No Date (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee, No Date (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Council To The Board Of Regents, March 1981 - May 1981 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, July 1981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, August 1-20, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, August 21-31 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, September 1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, October 1981 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, November 1981 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, December 1-21, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, December 22-30, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, January 1982 - April 1982 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, June 1982 - October 1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President: Presidential Evaluation, September 1981 - October 1981 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Search Committee - Selection Of The President, Publications, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Board of Regents—Tuition And Registration Fees, July 1981 – October 1981 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Series 3: Arizona State Bar Association, 1958-1979
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Arizona Bar Foundation, August 1979-September 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Committee to change uniform commercial code and uniform state law, October 1964-September 1965 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Committee on court of appeal, September 1964-September 1965 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Committee on the economics of law practice, August 1971-August 1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Committee on government relations, July 1967 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, April 1958-December 1958 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, January 1959-June 1959 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, July 1959-December 1959 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, January 1960-April 1960 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, May 1960-July 1960 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, August 1960-December 1960 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, January 1961-March 1961 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, April 1961-June 1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, July 1961-December 1961 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, January 1962-April 1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Correspondence, May 1962-October 1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Hearsay Rule in Arizona, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Minutes, January 1958-April 1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Bar Association—Minutes, May 1960-April 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Series 4: Arizona State Board of Education, 1965 – 1977
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Bylaws, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Compact for Education, September 1965 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Conferences: Compact For Education, September 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Conferences: National Association of State Boards of Education, Portland, Oregon, October 13-15, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, March 1965 – April 1965 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, May 1965 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, June 1965 – July 1965 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, August 1965 – September 1965 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, October 1965 – November 1965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, December 1965 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, January 1966 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, February 1966 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, March 1966 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, April 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, May 1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, June 1966 – July 1966 (Box 46, Folder 3)